{
  "rounds": [
    {
      "round_name": "The Baby",
      "question": "P letter foods like pears, peaches, prunes help fix .....",
      "solution": "constipation",
      "answer": "(our pediatrician)"
    },
    {
      "round_name": "The Baby",
      "question": "Spurgeon, Orange and Ples were popular ..... in late 1800s/early 1900s",
      "solution": "names",
      "answer": "the big fat activity book for pregnant people - jordan reid and erin williams"
    },
    {
      "round_name": "The Baby",
      "question": "On a baby, where would you find the fontanelles?",
      "solution": "head",
      "answer": "Fontanelles allow skull to compress during birth so it can pass through the birth canal."
    },
    {
      "round_name": "The Baby",
      "question": "The tar-like, sticky black poo that newborns initially poop, is called ....._",
      "solution": "meconium",
      "answer": "Children's Knowledge Bank - Part i."
    },
    {
      "round_name": "The Baby",
      "question": "A study in 2009 suggested that english speaking toddlers as young as 2, could guess ..... of words.",
      "solution": "plural",
      "answer": "Journal of Child Language in 2009, Jennifer Zapf and Linda Smith,"
    },
    {
      "round_name": "Who said WHAT?",
      "question": "“Raising kids is part joy and part ......” — Ed Asner",
      "solution": "guerrilla warfare",
      "answer": "Says the internet. Also look up Ed Asner, because I don't know who he is."
    },
    {
      "round_name": "Who said WHAT?",
      "question": "“Having a new baby is like suddenly getting the world’s worst ......” — Anne Lamott",
      "solution": "roommate",
      "answer": "Says the Internet."
    },
    {
      "round_name": "Who said WHAT?",
      "question": "“Becoming a mom to me means that you have accepted that for the next 16 years of your life, you will have a sticky ......” - Nia Vardalos",
      "solution": "purse",
      "answer": "intrwbz"
    },
    {
      "round_name": "Who said WHAT?",
      "question": "“A two-year old is kind of like having a ....., but you don't have a top for it.” - Jerry Seinfeld",
      "solution": "blender",
      "answer": "GoodHouseKeeping..."
    },
    {
      "round_name": "Who said WHAT?",
      "question": "“When I tell my kids I'll do something in a minute, what I'm really saying is 'Please ......'” - @SarcasticMommy4",
      "solution": "forget",
      "answer": "@SarcasticMommy4 twitters."
    }
  ]
}